Guide to the AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1944-2000; 1970-2000; 0450-017; 44.48 cubic ft. 44 boxes
  - PERSONNEL ADMINISTRATION RECORDS, 1954- 1992; SERIES XI (Box-folder 18/3-18/23)
    - United Pacific Life Insurance Company, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 18/17)
    - Retreat notes, 1988 (Box-folder 18/18)
    - National Opinion Panel survey, 1987 (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Steering Committee for the Employee Benefit Specialist Program, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 18/20)
    - Washington Office Employees Security Fund Arbitration Case, 1981 (Box-folder 18/21)
    - Washington Office Employees Security Trust Fund: Operations Manual, 1979 (Box-folder 18/22)
    - Trust Agreement: Washington Office Employees Security Fund, 1976 (Box-folder 18/23)
  - PLANT ADMINISTRATION RECORDS, 1963-1984; SERIES XII (Box-folder 18/24-18/33)
    - Office lease agreement and correspondence, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 18/24)
    - First and Cedar Building: mail room, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 18/25)
    - Office move to Bay Vista, 1981- 1982 (Box-folder 18/26)
    - Bay Vista Building Co., Inc., 1980-1984 (Box-folder 18/27)
    - Bay Vista Building Co., Inc.: correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 18/28)
    - 314 First Avenue West:: appraisal report, 1991 (Box-folder 18/29)
    - Olympia office lease, 1960-1980 (Box-folder 18/30)
    - Olympia office move, 1978- 1981 (Box-folder 18/31)
    - Olympia office equipment, 1973 (Box-folder 18/32)
    - Building site offers, 1969- 1970 (Box-folder 18/33)
  - POSITION PAPERS, 1979-1994; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 18/34 -19/5)
    - Legislative position statements, 1979- 1981 (Box-folder 18/34)
    - Legislative position statements, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 18/35)
    - Legislative position statements, 1986 (Box-folder 18/36)
    - Legislative position statements, 1987 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Legislative position statements, 1988- 1989 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Legislative position statements, 1990 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Legislative position statements, 1991 (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Legislative position statements, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 19/5)
  - SPEAKERS BUREAU RECORDS, 1987-2000; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 19/6-19/15)
    - Correspondence, 1987- 1988 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Background information, 1987-1900 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Volunteers, 1999- 2000 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - School-to-work Consortia mailing, 1999 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Labor in the Community newsletter, 1988- 1990 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - Request forms, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Request forms, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Request forms, 1990- 1991 (Box-folder 19/13)
    - Request forms, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 19/14)
    - Feedback forms (Box-folder 19/15)
  - STAFF MEETING MINUTES, 1987-1988; SERIES XV (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Minutes, 1987- 1988 (Box-folder 19/16)
  - STANDING COMMITTEE RECORDS AND CORRESPONDENCE, 1975-2001; SERIES XVI (Box-folder 19/17 -21/16)
    - Nominations, 1987 (Box-folder 19/17)
    - Nominations, 1989 (Box-folder 19/18)
    - Nominations, 1990 (Box-folder 19/19)
    - Nominations, 1991 (Box-folder 19/20)
    - Nominations, 1992 (Box-folder 19/21)
    - Nominations, 1993 (Box-folder 19/22)
    - Nominations, 1997 (Box-folder 19/23)
    - Nominations, 1998 (Box-folder 19/24)
    - Nominations, 1999 (Box-folder 19/25)
    - Black Caucus, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 19/26)
    - Black Caucus, 1993 (Box-folder 19/27)
    - Economic Development and Job Retention Committee, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Education, Training and Apprenticeship Committee, 1986 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Education, Training and Apprenticeship Training, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Employment and Unemployment Committee, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Organizing Committee, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Political Action Committee, 1994- 1996 (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Public Employee Committee: membership and formation -- Part 1, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Public Employee Committee: membership and formation -- Part 2, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - Public Employee Committee, 1987 (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Public Employee Committee, 1988 (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Public Employee Conference, 1988 (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Public Employee Committee, 1989 (Box-folder 20/12)
    - Public Employee Conference, 1989 (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Public Employee Committee, 1990 (Box-folder 20/14)
    - Public Employee Conference, 1990 (Box-folder 20/15)
    - Public Employee Committee, 1991 (Box-folder 20/16)
    - Public Employee Conference, 1991 (Box-folder 20/17)
    - Public Employee Conference, 1998 (Box-folder 20/18)
    - Public Employee Committee: appointments, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 20/19)
    - Transportation Committee, 1997- 2001 (Box-folder 20/20)
    - WISHA Monitoring Committee, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 20/21)
    - WISHA Monitoring Committee, 1985- 1986 (Box-folder 20/22)
    - WISHA Monitoring Committee, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 20/23)
    - WISHA Monitoring Committee, 1997 (Box-folder 20/24)
    - WISHA Monitoring Committee, 1998 (Box-folder 20/25)
    - WISHA Monitoring Committee, 1999 (Box-folder 20/26)
    - WISHA Monitoring Committee, 2000 (Box-folder 20/27)
    - Women's Committee membership - Part 1, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 20/28)
    - Women's Committee membership - Part 2, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 20/29)
    - Women's Committee minutes, 1984- 1986 (Box-folder 20/30)
    - Women's Committee workshops, 1986 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Women's Committee reunion, 1987 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Women's Committee, 1990 (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Women's Committee, 1994 (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Women's Committee, 1995 (Box-folder 21/5)
    - Women's Committee, 1996 (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Women's Committee, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 21/7)
    - Women's Committee: Conference on Women in the Work Force, 1976 (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Women's Committee: Spring Conference, 1977 (Box-folder 21/9)
    - Women's Committee: Spring Conference in Pasco and Seattle, 1978 (Box-folder 21/10)
    - Women's Committee: Conference on Health and Safety for Women Workers, 1980 (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Women's Committee: Conference on Sexual Harassment on the Job, 1980 (Box-folder 21/12)
    - Women's Committee: Conference on Organizing and Leadership Development for Women, Seattle, 1981 (Box-folder 21/13)
    - Women's Committee: Conference on Organizing and Leadership Development for Women, Spokane, 1981 (Box-folder 21/14)
    - Women's Committee: Working Women's Legislative Forum, 1983 (Box-folder 21/15)
    - Women's Committee: Women's Conference, 1995 (Box-folder 21/16)
  - WSLC SECTION RECORDS, 1957-1982; SERIES XVII (Box-folder 21/17-21/28)
    - General and circular correspondence, 1964-1980 (Box-folder 21/17)
    - Contributions to Seattle Worker Center, 1991 (Box-folder 21/18)
    - Building Trades Section, 1962-1976 (Box-folder 21/19)
    - Food and Beverage Trades Section, 1961- 1980 (Box-folder 21/20)
    - Industrial Unions Section affiliates, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 21/21)
    - Industrial Unions Section: constitution, 1960-1972 (Box-folder 21/22)
    - Industrial Unions Section: officers, 1963-1982 (Box-folder 21/23)
    - Maritime Trades Section, 1964- 1976 (Box-folder 21/24)
    - Metal Trades Section, 1957-1980 (Box-folder 21/25)
    - Miscellaneous Trades Section, 1962- 1984 (Box-folder 21/26)
    - Miscellaneous Trades Section: annual and executive board meetings, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 21/27)
    - Miscellaneous Trades Section: officers and constitution, 1963-1980 (Box-folder 21/28)
  - WELFARE AND PENSION ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES INC. RECORDS, 1963- 1987; SERIES XVIII (Box-folder 21/29-21/32)
    - History and sale, 1972-1987 (Box-folder 21/29)
    - Office plant, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 21/30)
    - 2701 First Ave. building, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 21/31)
    - Bankers Life Pension Plan GA 8566, 1971- 1974 (Box-folder 21/32)
  - WSLC PPP COMMITTEE PUBLIC DISCLOSURE COMMISSION REPORTS AND CORRESPONDENCE, 1975-2009; SERIES XIX (Box-folder 21/33 -22/3; 43/4-6)
    - Correspondence, 1975- 1984 (Box-folder 21/33)
    - PDC reports, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 21/34)
    - PDC reports, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 21/35)
    - PDC reports, 1982 (Box-folder 21/36)
    - PDC reports, 1983 (Box-folder 21/37)
    - PDC reports, 1984 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - PDC reports, 1985 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Paycheck Protection Coalition, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - PPP contribution summaries, 1996 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - PPP contribution tracking sheets, 1997 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - PAC contributions, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 43/6)
  - STRIKE, BOYCOTT, UNFAIR LIST RECORDS, 1979-1995; SERIES XX (Box-folder 22/4-22/12)
    - Lockouts and Unemployment Compensation, 1990 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - AFSCME Council 2 boycott request, 1992 (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Channel 11 Unfair List proceedings, 1983- 1984 (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Chateau Ste. Michelle/Stimson Lane Wines boycott, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Coors Boycott Committee, 1979- 1981 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Kelso Firefighters, 1987 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Rainier Brewery boycott, 1995 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - 1990 Safeway Boycott (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Security Pacific Bank boycott, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 22/12)
  - EXECUTIVE BOARD ELECTION RECORDS, 1985-1998; SERIES XXI (Box-folder 22/13-22/28)
    - Officer election, 1985 (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Nominations, 1985 (Box-folder 22/14)
    - Ballots, 1985 (Box-folder 22/15)
    - Working file, 1985 (Box-folder 22/16)
    - Election report, 1985 (Box-folder 22/17)
    - Nominations, 1987 (Box-folder 22/18)
    - Working file, 1987 (Box-folder 22/19)
    - Election report, 1987 (Box-folder 22/20)
    - Nominations, 1989 (Box-folder 22/21)
    - Election report, 1989 (Box-folder 22/22)
    - Election process, 1991 (Box-folder 22/23)
    - Nominations, 1991 (Box-folder 22/24)
    - Ballot, 1991 (Box-folder 22/25)
    - Election report, 1991 (Box-folder 22/26)
    - Election report, 1993 (Box-folder 22/27)
    - Nominations, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 22/28)
  - POLITICAL ACTIVITIES RECORDS, 1963-2000; SERIES XXII (Box-folder 22/29-24/23; 43/7-39)
    - A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1978- 1983 (Box-folder 22/29)
    - All-night convenience store security: legislation, 1988 (Box-folder 22/30)
    - Child labor, 1995 (Box-folder 22/31)
    - Civil Rights: AFL-CIO statements, 1963-1978 (Box-folder 22/32)
    - Columbia Basin Institute, 1988- 1982 (Box-folder 22/33)
    - Congressional legislation, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 22/34)
    - Drug testing legislation, 1987- 1988 (Box-folder 22/35)
    - Election day volunteers - Part 1, 1996 (Box-folder 22/36)
    - Election day volunteers - Part 2, 1996 (Box-folder 22/37)
    - Election day volunteers - Part 3, 1996 (Box-folder 22/38)
    - Energized and Organized Vote Campaign 96, 1996 (Box-folder 22/39)
    - ESSB 5156 veto override, 1995 (Box-folder 22/40)
    - Extremist file, c. 1965 (Box-folder 22/41)
    - Frontlash, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 22/42)
    - Get Out the Vote, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 22/43)
    - Health care reform, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Labor Group on Health Care Reform, 1994- 1997 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Initiative 245: background, legal opinion etc., 1968 (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Initiative 245: analysis of consumer credit legislation, 1968 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Initiative 245: petitions, 1968 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Initiative 245: election statistics, 1968 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Initiative 245: daily reports on petitions, 1968 (Box-folder 23/7)
    - Initiative 245: WSLC staff meetings and reports, 1968 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Initiative 245: pre-election campaign expenditures, 1968 (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Initiative 245: contributions for general election campaign, 1968 (Box-folder 23/10)
    - Initiative 245: cost report, 1968 (Box-folder 23/11)
    - Initiative 245: advertising budget radio, TV, newspapers, 1968 (Box-folder 23/12)
    - Initiative 245: brochures, 1968 (Box-folder 23/13)
    - Initiative 245: opposition, 1968 (Box-folder 23/14)
    - Initiative 245: letters to college presidents, 1968 (Box-folder 23/15)
    - Initiative 245: Sea-First Employees Association, 1968 (Box-folder 23/16)
    - Initiative 245: WSLC Reports newsletter, 1968 (Box-folder 23/17)
    - Initiative 245: speakers information kit, 1968 (Box-folder 23/18)
    - Initiative 245: speaking engagements, 1968 (Box-folder 23/19)
    - Initiative 245: Seattle P-I, 1968 (Box-folder 23/20)
    - Initiative 245: Seattle Times, 1968 (Box-folder 23/21)
    - Initiative 245: newspaper ads, 1968 (Box-folder 23/22)
    - Initiative 245: news releases, 1968 (Box-folder 23/23)
    - Initiative 245: TV and radio, 1968 (Box-folder 23/24)
    - Initiative 245: endorsements and signature gatherers "for" 245, 1968 (Box-folder 23/25)
    - Initiative 245: voters pamphlet, 1968 (Box-folder 23/26)
    - Initiative 518, 1988 (Box-folder 23/27)
    - Initiative 601 Group, 1999 (Box-folder 23/28)
    - Initiative 688 minimum wage campaign -- Part 1, 1998 (Box-folder 23/29)
    - Initiative 688 minimum wage campaign -- Part 2, 1998 (Box-folder 23/30)
    - Interest rate on consumer credit: correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 23/31)
    - Labor Issues Discussion Group, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 23/32)
    - Labor Lobby Day, 1984- 1985 (Box-folder 23/33)
    - Labor Roundtable, 1992 (Box-folder 23/34)
    - Labor Roundtable, 1994- 1997 (Box-folder 23/35)
    - Legislative Action Committee 9th CD, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 23/36)
    - Legislative report and voting records, 1979-1990 (Box-folder 23/37)
    - Legislature, 1982 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - 1993 Legislative session (Box-folder 24/2)
    - 1994 Legislative session - Part 1 (Box-folder 24/3)
    - 1994 Legislative session - Part 2 (Box-folder 24/4)
    - 1995 Legislative session (Box-folder 24/5)
    - 1995 Legislative session: House bills (Box-folder 24/6)
    - 1995 Legislative session: Senate bills (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Livable Wage Coalition, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Martin Luther King Jr. Holiday Commission, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Mental health legislation, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 24/10)
    - Phone banks, 1984 (Box-folder 24/11)
    - Political Wars, 1986 (Box-folder 24/12)
    - Polling activity, 1997 (Box-folder 24/13)
    - Progressive Legislative Discussion Group, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 24/14)
    - The 1996 Project (Box-folder 24/15)
    - Right to Know legislation, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 24/16)
    - Unemployment compensation legislation, 1965 (Box-folder 24/17)
    - Unemployment compensation: HB 28 and SB 28, 1965 (Box-folder 24/18)
    - Unemployment Insurance Trust Fund, 1995 (Box-folder 24/19)
    - Washington Health Services Act, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 24/20)
    - Workers' compensation: 3-way - Part 1, 1970-1981 (Box-folder 24/21)
    - Workers' compensation: 3-way - Part 2, 1970-1981 (Box-folder 24/22)
    - Workers' compensation: 3-way - Part 3, 1970-1981 (Box-folder 24/23)
    - Minimum wage polling, 1996 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - CURES campaign finance reform initiative, 1993 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - Property tax initiative, 1997 (Box-folder 43/9)
    - Referendum #48, stadium, 1997 (Box-folder 43/10)
    - Initiative 172, affirmative action, 1995 (Box-folder 43/11)
    - Initiative 173, school vouchers, 1995 (Box-folder 43/12)
    - Initiative 177, charter schools, 1995 (Box-folder 43/13)
    - Regional transit authority campaign, 1995 (Box-folder 43/14)
    - Presidents' Day Rally for Working Families, 1996 (Box-folder 43/15)
    - Washington State Democrats, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 43/16-19)
    - Washington State Democratic Convention, 1994 (Box-folder 43/20)
    - Democratic precinct caucus, 1996 (Box-folder 43/21)
    - COPE retiree consultant, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 43/22)
    - Local elections database, 1997 (Box-folder 43/23)
    - WSLC Local Elections Project, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 43/24)
    - 1995 Legislative session: bills (Box-folder 43/25-26)
    - 1996 Legislative session (Box-folder 43/27)
    - 1997 Legislative session (Box-folder 43/28)
    - 1997 Legislative session: bills (Box-folder 43/29)
    - Legislative Action Alerts, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 43/30)
    - Legislative Update, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 43/31)
    - WSLC Reports, 1997 (Box-folder 43/32)
    - Legislative Action Program, 1997 (Box-folder 43/33)
    - Congressional hunt committee, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 43/34)
    - Labor Roundtable, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 43/35)
    - Gang of Five, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 43/36-37)
    - Political Action Committee, 1997 (Box-folder 43/38)
    - United Labor Lobby minutes, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 43/39)
  - ELECTION CAMPAIGN RECORDS, 1978-1997; SERIES XXIII (Box-folder 25/1-25/20)
    - 38th District; Vognild vs. Mardesich, 1978 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Governor: McDermott vs. Spellman, 1980 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - US Senate: Gorton vs. Magnusson, 1979- 1980 (Box-folder 25/3)
    - US President, 1980 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Carter/Mondale Labor Committee, 1980 (Box-folder 25/5)
    - US Senator: Lowry vs. Evans, 1983 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - 1984 Election returns (Box-folder 25/7)
    - US Senator: Adams vs. Gorton, 1985- 1986 (Box-folder 25/8)
    - 1986 Election (Box-folder 25/9)
    - 1988 Election (Box-folder 25/10)
    - Campaign 1996, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 25/11)
    - Gang of Four, 1994 (Box-folder 25/12)
    - Gang of Four, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 25/13)
    - Gang of Four, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - 35th Legislative District Senate campaign - Part 1, 1997 (Box-folder 25/15)
    - 35th Legislative District Senate campaign - Part 2, 1997 (Box-folder 25/16)
    - 33th Legislative District House campaign - Part 1, 1997 (Box-folder 25/17)
    - 33th Legislative District House campaign - Part 2, 1997 (Box-folder 25/18)
    - 1998 Candidates (Box-folder 25/19)
    - 1992 Election (Box-folder 25/20)
  - AFL-CIO REPORTS AND CORRESPONDENCE, 1961-2006; SERIES XXIV (Box-folder 25/21-26/34)
    - General correspondence, 1995 (Box-folder 25/21)
    - General correspondence, 1996 (Box-folder 25/22)
    - General correspondence, 1994- 1997 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - General correspondence, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Annual reports from WSLC to AFL-CIO, 1961-1985 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - State and Local Central Bodies, 1961-1982 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - AFL-CIO Department of Organization, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - International Representatives in Washington State, 1971-1981 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - Convention proceedings, 1987 (Box-folder 26/7)
    - AFL-CIO newsletters, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 26/8)
    - Rules governing state and central bodies, 1958-1973 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - State per diem practices, 1985 (Box-folder 26/10)
    - New tax disclosure requirement, 1988 (Box-folder 26/11)
    - Policy Resolutions, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 26/12)
    - Policy Resolutions, 1983- 1985 (Box-folder 26/13)
    - Policy Resolutions, 1987 (Box-folder 26/14)
    - Policy Resolutions, 1989 (Box-folder 26/15)
    - Western States AFL-CIO Legislative Conference, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 42/8)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1977 (Box-folder 26/16)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1978 (Box-folder 26/17)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1979 (Box-folder 26/18)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1980 (Box-folder 26/19)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1981 (Box-folder 26/20)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1982 (Box-folder 26/21)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1983 (Box-folder 26/22)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1984 (Box-folder 26/23)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1985 (Box-folder 26/24)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1986 (Box-folder 26/25)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1987 (Box-folder 26/26)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1988 (Box-folder 26/27)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1989 (Box-folder 26/28)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1990 (Box-folder 26/29)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1991 (Box-folder 26/30)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1992 (Box-folder 26/31)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1995 (Box-folder 26/32)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council meetings, 1997-2006 (Box-folder 26/33)
    - Human Resources Development Institute, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 26/34)
  - WESTERN STATES COUNCIL, AFL-CIO RECORDS, 1991-2009; SERIES XXV (Box-folder 26/35-27/15; 42/8)
    - Dues per capita, 1998 (Box-folder 26/35)
    - Dues per capita, 1999 (Box-folder 26/36)
    - Dues per capita, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 26/37)
    - Financial records, 1998 (Box-folder 26/38)
    - Financial records, 1999 (Box-folder 26/39)
    - Financial records, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 26/40)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Committee 2000, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - 13 Western States Council Meeting, Las Vegas, 1998 (Box-folder 27/6)
    - Meeting on Inter-Organizational Communications, 1998 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - 13 Western States Council Meeting, Santa Fe, 1998 (Box-folder 27/8)
    - 13 Western States Council Meeting, Seattle, 1999 (Box-folder 27/9)
    - Western States AFL-CIO meeting slide show, 2003 (Box-folder 27/10)
    - Western States AFL-CIO meeting, May 2005 (Box-folder 27/11)
    - Western States AFL-CIO meeting, December 2005 (Box-folder 27/12)
    - Western States AFL-CIO meeting, December 2006 (Box-folder 27/13)
    - Western States AFL-CIO meeting, December 2007 (Box-folder 27/14)
    - Western States AFL-CIO meeting, December 2008 (Box-folder 27/15)
  - INTERNATIONAL, NATIONAL, AND REGIONAL UNIONS: REPORTS AND CORRESPONDENCE, 1933-2008; SERIES XXVI (Box-folder 27/16-27/62)
    - Multiple addressee correspondence, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 27/16)
    - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1979 (Box-folder 27/17)
    - Air Line Pilots Association, 1977- 1978 (Box-folder 27/18)
    - Aluminum Workers International Union, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 27/19)
    - American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, 1951-1966 (Box-folder 27/20)
    - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, - 1983 (Box-folder 27/21)
    - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, 1980-1997 (Box-folder 27/22)
    - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 27/23)
    - International Chemical Workers Union, 1974 (Box-folder 27/24)
    - Communications Workers of America, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 27/25)
    - Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers International Union, 1980 (Box-folder 27/26)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1970-1982 (Box-folder 27/27)
    - International Union of Elevator Constructors, 1981 (Box-folder 27/28)
    - International Union of Operating Engineers, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 27/29)
    - United Farm Workers, 1970- 1975 (Box-folder 27/30)
    - United Farm Workers of Washington State, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 27/31)
    - International Association of Fire Fighters, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 27/32)
    - United Food and Commercial Workers, 1956-1983 (Box-folder 27/33)
    - United Furniture Workers of America, 1982 (Box-folder 27/34)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1933-1981 (Box-folder 27/35)
    - Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the US and Canada, 1979 (Box-folder 27/36)
    - American Flint Glass Workers Union, c. 1978 (Box-folder 27/37)
    - American Federation of Government Employees, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 27/38)
    - National Hospital Union, 1983 (Box-folder 27/39)
    - Hotel and Restaurant Employees' and Bartenders' International Union, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 27/40)
    - Laborers' International Union of North America, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 27/41)
    - National Association of Letter Carriers, 1981 (Box-folder 27/42)